couponsherpa.com 2019-01-29

# Privacy Policy for CouponSherpa.com

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, download our mobile applications or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

The Coupon Sherpa app can share collected location data for Interest-Based Advertising: Allowing Advertisers to infer interests and serve ads to users based on their app activity and location data over time.

Android App: You can opt-out from any interest-based advertising. Go on Google Settings, Ads and then click on "Disable ads based on interests". When you have opted out using this setting on a device, advertisers will not use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests or serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.

iOS App: You can opt-out from any interest-based advertising. Go on Settings. Privacy, Advertising and then click on "Limit Ad-tracking". When you have opted out using this setting on a device, advertisers will not use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests or serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  *  To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  *  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  *  To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used  to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

In addition to other information described in this policy, we may collect and share precise location information through methods such as mobile “SDKs” through our partnership with [Cuebiq](http://privacy.cuebiq.com/) which assists in covering the costs of developing and maintaining this app and related services. This information may be used by itself, aggregated, or combined with mobile identifiers (such as IDFAs and Android IDs), and shared with other parties, for purposes related to advertising, attribution (e.g., measuring ad performance), analytics and research.  You can remove your consent to having your location data collected by changing the settings on your device (note that certain services may lose functionality as a result). You can also control options through your [device’s opt-out settings](http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice) which will tell advertisers to not use your in-app information from that device to collect and serve interest-based advertising and will inform our partner, Cuebiq, to halt further data collection and sharing from this device.

We use [Sense360](http://sense360.com/), a third party technology provider, to help us better understand how our users use our app and their devices. Coupon Sherpa sends raw sensor data generated by your device to Sense360. This sensor data may include information from GPS receivers, accelerometers, gyroscopes, and other sensors, which may allow Sense360 to determine, for example, your device’s location, acceleration, and orientation. Sense360 may use this information to send us analytics reports regarding how our users are using [our app] and their devices, or for other purposes including market research and analytics. To learn more, please visit Sense360’s privacy policy, available at <https://sense360.com/privacy-policy/>

We use advertising/technology services from a third party called inMarket which may use device and location data to provide advertisements for and anonymous analytics to goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To see inMarket’s full Privacy Policy, please visit [https://inmarket.com/privacy_policy/](https://t.yesware.com/tt/a26d5004bec00d70b6f0376ea7388b2338104c91/1c7cd2323863e3e4d7ffeaf23f1a79fa/bc5229a56f87312e8f611d4ec00f260e/inmarket.com/privacy_policy/)

You can opt-out from any interest-based advertising through your device settings. When you have opted out using this setting on a device, advertisers will not use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests or serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.

**Do we use cookies and web beacons?** We and the third parties we authorize may receive and store certain types of non-personally identifiable information whenever you interact with us by using "cookies", "web beacons" and analogous technology. "Cookies" are small files that are placed on your computer or your internet browser memory to enable the owner of the cookie to recognize your browser and to provide convenience and other features to you. It is important to note that the cookies that we use, or permit others to use, do not contain and are not tied to personally-identifiable information about you. You may be able to direct your internet browser not to allow cookies and you can typically delete existing cookies from your computer at any time. Please note, however, if you set such browser settings or delete existing cookies then some elements of our website may not function properly or be available to you.

We also work with and permit certain third parties, including, but not limited to advertising networks and website analysis firms, to place cookies on your computer or browser when you view, click or otherwise interact with advertisements that are featured on our website. These third party cookies and analogous technology are used to gather non-personally identifiable information about your activities on our website and third party sites you may visit to serve you with advertisements that are relevant to your interests and preferences while you are on third party sites. Some of these third parties participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different web sites. To learn more and make choices about preference-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the DAA website at www.aboutads.info.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. We may anonymously share your location, excluding personally identifiable information, with third party advertisers to enhance your experience with more relevant, location-based offers.

 **Do we have affiliate relationships with the merchants on this site?**  
We do have affiliate relationships with most of the merchants on CouponSherpa.com. This site accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. The compensation may influence the content on this website.

 **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
 **  
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
 **  
** **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
We may update or change this Policy from time to time, with or without any advance notice. The date of the last change or update to this Policy shall be noted at the end of this Policy, and any changes made will be effective upon posting of the revised version. If there are material changes in the way we handle your personally-identifiable information, or to the Policy itself, including changes to the Preference Based Advertising practices set forth above, we will notify you using direct means, at our discretion – either through displaying a notice on our website or by sending you an email, so that you may review the changed terms and consent to them prior to continuing to use our website. We encourage you to check this policy whenever you use our website and services to understand how your personal information is used.

 **Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

8342 Golden Eagle Rd  
Fort Collins, CO 80528
